codeitpretty.com 2013-05-26

# Code it Pretty: Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

I take your privacy seriously. This policy describes what personal information is collected and how it is used. (This privacy policy is applicable to www.codeitpretty.com.)

**Routine Information Collection**

All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes, and lets me know what pages and information are useful and helpful to visitors.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

This blog uses Google Analytics and Clicky to track pageviews and visits. No personally identifying information is gathered by either service.

Some advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. The advertising here comes from: Google Adsense, Amazon, and Passionfruit Ads.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies. 

**Controlling Your Privacy**

Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms. You can also visit [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) for more information on how cookies work and how to disable cookies in your browser or on specific websites.
